Max Tennis Theater Playbill Collection MS013
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Max Tennis Theater Playbill Collection
1935 -- 1980
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tennis, Max
MS013
39 Volumes
Arrangement
The collection is organized into one series called 'Theater playbills.'
Scope and Contents
A collection of twentieth-century theater programs and playbills from Boston and New York theaters, collected by Max Tennis, A1916. An inventory listing the productions by year is available in the collection documentation folder. The inventory indicates that Max Tennis' collection at one time contained play programs from the years 1915 to 1935, but these programs are not part of this collection.
Please contact the DCA for more information.
Biographical / Historical
Max Tennis received his bachelor of arts and science from Tufts in 1916 and then worked as chemical engineer in Alaska before joining the army during World War I. He graduated from Harvard Medical School in 1922 and continued to study pediatric medicine in London, Berlin, and Vienna among other cities. Working as pediatrician in Boston, he was also on the staff at several local hospitals, among them Beth Israel and Boston's Children's Hospital. Given his enjoyment of the arts, he also worked as "consulting physician for various companies performing in Boston." Max Tennis died on February 12, 1987.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Tennis, Max; Alumni collections; Greater Boston arts
- Theater playbills, 1935 -- 1980; MS013.001; 39 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains a collection of twentieth-century theater programs and playbills from Boston and New York theaters, collected by Max Tennis, A1916.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Playbills, 1935 -- 1939; MS013.001.001.001 (Box Volume 1)
  - Playbills, 1940 -- 1944; MS013.001.002.001 (Box Volume 2)
  - Playbills, 1944 -- 1945; MS013.001.003.001 (Box Volume 3)
  - Playbills, 1946; MS013.001.004.001 (Box Volume 4)
  - Playbills, 1946 -- 1947; MS013.001.005.001 (Box Volume 5)
  - Playbills, 1947 -- 1948; MS013.001.006.001 (Box Volume 6)
  - Playbills, 1948; MS013.001.007.001 (Box Volume 7)
  - Playbills, 1948 -- 1949; MS013.001.008.001 (Box Volume 8)
  - Playbills, 1949 -- 1951; MS013.001.009.001 (Box Volume 9)
  - Playbills, 1951; MS013.001.010.001 (Box Volume 10)
  - Playbills, 1951 -- 1953; MS013.001.011.001 (Box Volume 11)
  - Playbills, 1953 -- 1954; MS013.001.012.001 (Box Volume 12)
  - Playbills, 1954 -- 1955; MS013.001.013.001 (Box Volume 13)
  - Playbills, 1955 -- 1957; MS013.001.014.001 (Box Volume 14)
  - Playbills, 1957 -- 1958; MS013.001.015.001 (Box Volume 15)
  - Playbills, 1958 -- 1959; MS013.001.016.001 (Box Volume 16)
  - Playbills, 1959 -- 1960; MS013.001.017.001 (Box Volume 17)
  - Playbills, 1960 -- 1961; MS013.001.018.001 (Box Volume 18)
  - Playbills, 1961 -- 1962; MS013.001.019.001 (Box Volume 19)
  - Playbills, 1962 -- 1963; MS013.001.020.001 (Box Volume 20)
  - Playbills, 1963 -- 1964; MS013.001.021.001 (Box Volume 21)
  - Playbills, 1964; MS013.001.022.001 (Box Volume 22)
  - Playbills, 1964 -- 1965; MS013.001.023.001 (Box Volume 23)
  - Playbills, 1965; MS013.001.024.001 (Box Volume 24)
  - Playbills, 1965 -- 1966; MS013.001.025.001 (Box Volume 25)
  - Playbills, 1966; MS013.001.026.001 (Box Volume 26)
  - Playbills, 1966 -- 1967; MS013.001.027.001 (Box Volume 27)
  - Playbills, 1967; MS013.001.028.001 (Box Volume 28)
  - Playbills, 1967 -- 1968; MS013.001.029.001 (Box Volume 29)
  - Playbills, 1968; MS013.001.030.001 (Box Volume 30)
  - Playbills, 1968 -- 1969; MS013.001.031.001 (Box Volume 31)
  - Playbills, 1969; MS013.001.032.001 (Box Volume 32)
  - Playbills, 1969 -- 1970; MS013.001.033.001 (Box Volume 33)
  - Playbills, 1970 -- 1971; MS013.001.034.001 (Box Volume 34)
  - Playbills, 1971 -- 1973; MS013.001.035.001 (Box Volume 35)
  - Playbills, 1973 -- 1974; MS013.001.036.001 (Box Volume 36)
  - Playbills, 1974 -- 1975; MS013.001.037.001 (Box Volume 37)
  - Playbills, 1975 -- 1977; MS013.001.038.001 (Box Volume 38)
  - Playbills, 1977 -- 1980; MS013.001.039.001 (Box Volume 39)